Hey. Hi Dorothy.
How are you doing?
Oh good.
I feel like I just had a very long call with Alexander to set up archive in local environments.
So I've been playing around my.
I've been splitting my days into product to DOS and GTM to do today, like product and analytics to do.
So it's like crazy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm. I'm not splitting my days.
I just have like a bunch of things at the same time going on. But I mean it's okay.
I think it's.
It's always refreshing working in lots of things because I mean I think that all projects we do are valuable.
So it's great. So cool. Basically. Yeah, I forgot to update the title. I don't know what happened.
It didn't even have Zoom link, but okay.
I'm running a summit rapid because something that Paul wanted to do is to lock the potential dates for next
global summit. And we are also going to plan team summit. It will be potentially with engineering team.
I think that since it's our biggest team and they are all like in same, almost all in the same
region, we are thinking to potentially planning one around that team as well.
So yeah, basically we are thinking on end of Q2 for a team summit would be something around May and
June and Q4 for global summit which could be October, November.
So the main thing I'm running right now is that I lock time with all the exact team members to
gather the availability throughout those dates to you know, like some people have planned.
For example Vlad already have a trip plan in June so would love to know your availability.
I have a spreadsheet.
I did it at the same time I send you on the Zoom chat, the spreadsheet so you can pull
it and yeah, basically Mark, if whether you are free or it's not ideal or you're busy, if you already
have plans on any of those states.
So yeah, that's. That's basically one of my main goals here. Okay.
Yeah. Oh. All right. Q4 over both. Okay, never mind. I don't have anything planned. Honestly.
My plan was around November. So I think we're all good for now. Around November,
Around you Thanksgiving. So I don't think it. It matters because.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think we are going to lock anything close to USA Thanksgiving because this last summit almost overlapped and
for something members it was like okay, but I need to travel later. Whatever. Like it was.
I think that at the end of the day was good for everyone. Like day was not that bad.
Like first week of December is not. I think it's not that crazy. But yeah. I mean let's see.
I'll double check. Like maybe I'm. I'll be out a few.
Like just one, two days or something to that sort. Because as. Let me double check because May, for instance.
Wait. So Q2 will. Even if it's engineering team, will we be needed there?
I still don't know.
I'm asking all the tech team members like everyone that is on the tech team, including you and N.
Just to make sure you're available. I don't.
I don't know if we are going to include everyone yet if all the exact team is going to be
there.
So I just want to know availability and I think that it could be interesting given you're working on product.
And one idea that Andrew gave me is that we should lock it during cycle planning. Like at least retro.
So I mean so that way we could work on roadmap. And I think.
I think it could be interesting to have you there as well.
But I'm gonna like on that call as well. Yeah.
Because what I was thinking is if it's Q2, I'll be out around doesn't matter like first week of May.
So I think it's fine like just a few. Just like one day in May. Never mind.
It's a Sunday, so I don't think it matters.
Okay, sounds good. And November would be around USA Thanksgiving, right?
Yes, I would be available at that time. I think.
You want Thanksgiving.
Yep. No. So I can just mark this as. Yeah.
Market as not ideal. So. I know. Yep. Already. Cool. Okay, sounds great.
Cool. Thank you, Dorothy.
I'm gonna be working as well on researching some locations given you know, visa timelines and all this stuff. Yeah.
So we should be good there as well. But yeah.
If you have suddenly any other thoughts, any other ideas, please let me know.
So you already know that I'm actively working on summit again. So yeah, that.
Which is wow. Because it's like if it's on May and October, I mean.
Oh yeah, for May, I mean it's kind of close so it makes sense.
But for October, November, I mean it's great that we're planning ahead.
So really, I mean I feel like everything is so close.
It's like January is already like, it's already last week of January. Like next week is February. I'm like, what?
But I feel like. But I feel like January has been forever. You know, it's like so long.
But after I feel like a lot of stuff has happened.
I know it's like it's not ending what is going on, but at the same time it's like, oh, it
already ended. Cool. Yeah.
Right. So yeah, I think it would be helpful.
I'll do a quick pass on this later today so I get you updated on some of those dates that
I won't be available.
But I don't think it's going to be like a week long or something to that sort.
It's just going to be one day, two days and mostly will be around the weekends.
But yeah, I would appreciate. So for instance, if the May, the May summit we will be a part of.
To your point, visas are really hard here in the Philippines and so if there.
I totally get you.
Yeah. So if there's like any like more details that we can use prior to that
right now Evgen suggested doing it in Poland given most of the team is located there and they are like
closer. So it could be like cheaper in terms of flights.
But that's something I'm going to double check and confirm because maybe it's cheaper on flights but accommodation is expensive.
So if the accommodation is too expensive, it's like okay, maybe we could do something meet.
So Vlad is pushing to doing it in Turkey again because he doesn't need visa.
He also recommend me to search Serbia.
Like it seems that that country is not that dangerous and he doesn't need visa.
Most of the team doesn't need.
So I mean I will do the research just to double check and I think that Vlad is going to
be in Turkey around June so maybe he can overlap the trip.
So yeah, I mean I will double check those locations as well.
I do like a couple like some high level research for the Pot summit, given engineering locations and continue working
on potential locations for Global summit.
All right, thank you. Yep.
Okay. If you have any other ideas, let me know.
Super happy to hear all the thoughts you can have guys. And yeah, that will be it for now.
I'm gonna.
I'm gonna prepare a doc with a couple of proposed solutions, and I will share it by end of week.
All right. Thanks, Emily. See ya.
Bye. Bye.